

ABOUT ME

Hello! My name is Cain, and I am a 22year-old Media Arts student currently pursuing my Batchelor's Degree with a minor in Business Administration at the University of Montana in Missoula, Montana.

Born & raised in the small town of Sturgis, South Dakota, I find myself grasping at any and all opportunities to experience new places, and to meet new & exciting people along the way.

CONTACT

PHONE: (605) 499-9041

ADDRESS: 425 S. 5th St. E. Missoula, MT 59801

EMAIL:

CainFritz@gmail.com

MY PASSIONS

- Graphic Design, Typography, & Color Design
- ♦ DIY Music Production
- Admiring Local Architecture
- Maintaining a Healthy and Holistic Lifestyle

CAIN **FRITZ**

Resume 2021

EDUCATION

Sturgis Brown High School

2013 - 2017

Obtained High School diploma from SBHS while attending honors placement courses as well as receiving dual-enrollment course credits.

University of Montana

2018 - Present

3rd year student at U of M currently pursuing bachelor's degree in media arts with a declared minor in business administration.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Traffic Control Services (TSC) – General Labor/Sub-Contractor May 2019 – August 2019

Duties as traffic control assistant at TSC included; preparing and dismantling traffic projects, operating heavy equipment, and working with a small, hard-working team to meet the individual needs of clients.

Hunter Bay Coffee Roasters - Barista

December 2019 – September 2020

Responsibilities as barista and small order cook at Hunter Bay included; assisting customers with product information, communicating with staff members to maximize efficiency, and preparing outgoing products.

University of Montana – Maintenance Assistant

August 2019 - December 2019 / August 2020 - Present Nightly custodial assistant for University of Montana currently completing routine maintenance tasks independently, while closely monitoring needs of the building in order to prepare facilities for the next instructional day.

SKILLS

- Superior communication skills
- Effective team player
- Consistent Midwestern work ethic
- Diverse experience in various occupations